<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="11" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
<i>Silence of sight the muse sought. When the sound is what constitutes existence if it is composed of thought.</i>

<i>Down the staircase the muse walked.</i>

<i>A sound consumed all the talk.</i>

<i>The third hour of dusk, after the second set, a sweat soaked body awoke and reality and the muse met. Their minds floating above unaware what the composition was of. A silhouette danced away from the stage. The audience in awe from its movements. Its dance full of rage.</i>

<i>Ripples of emotion swept the mass. The ethereal blanket swirled when it came to pass.</i>

<i>...And soft against the dimming sight...</i>

<i>The echo of ((<i>GO</i>)) faded into the night.</i>

<i>Its body shuttered. The muse's sight fluttered.</i>

<i>It held the tempo's exponential race. Those around slowed to watch the pace. The occurrences, amplitudes of time: Pop of Stance with Clip of Chime.</i>

<i>...bass hit, its body rippled, the glow slow to fade...</i>

<i>It moved.</i>

<i>A percussive chirp reverbed from the speaker's case. It spun when anyone looked to its face.</i>

<i>,,</i>Go<i>:'' Shallow wisp. Beat restrained bling. The crowd raised their wrists. Their mouths began to sing. The Crowns fell to the floor (The Shades before the door).</i>

<i>The entity  flipped</i>

<i>Shocked - Popped.</i>

<i>The lights dropped.</i>

<i>The thought</i> Need to see.

<i>So the muse could say ,,What could you be?''</i>

<i>The muse wanted to give unto it. A whisper. A shriek. Invoke the mind to move mouth. Gather the focus to form phonetic sound. The lips and tongue to rhyme. The muse wanted to give unto it. But the muse knew not what to</i>
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
