<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="15" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
fifteen. Tongue tasted salt from last night. Nose, numb from body sweat and motionless air, sniffed. Mind ticked: <i>Naked</i> <i>Time</i>: hands on nipples: Ten and Three. Palms closed spread sheet of TIME, masturbated. Finger/digits held time, zipped pants, fluffed couch, locked door, wiggled through hall and over green and red upon floor, snapped with whistle between isles decorated by tinder boxes, picture frames, cotton cushions, wax wick, wooden rods and felt the texture of pine and cedar, paused (palms covered mouth): ,,Fes!'' tapped pyramid of plastic dolls in rhythm to piano melody revised for consumer mind. ''Fes!'' and Customer Number Three rubbed fabric...Customer Number Three adjusted overalls, interrupted child-upon-palm's attempt to pull hair, pick nose, grab for dipper bag.

Fes laughed, smiled with the inhale of baby powder - caught in transfer - motioned an angled index | finger: Away Pink. 

''Fes,'' Jeff with slow echo ((''F e s'')). Digits scratched scalp. Palm dusted dander.

Fes's sight caught Jeff. Sight's Site jittered between customer, pink, blue (customer said ,,Unisex. Need both'') then to Manager Jeff's composure near doll pyramid. Vest in the stead of coat. Lenses in the stead of shades. Motion of digits discrete. 

,,Excuse me,'' smiled Fes: Swallowed the gum, paused to inspect sequins, tapped close to camouflage, rubbed lip while feigning attention toward Exit Door ''Yes, Jeffrey.''

Jeff's arms spread to make a statement the question ,,The silk is?''

Fes snapped indices ,,By the mail-order catalogs.''

Jeff waved away smoke smell, marched to Fes. 

They marched to lead of Jeff before silk display ,,I specifically told...-Why. Are. These. Holes. Here.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
