<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="17" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
...<i>Her</i> #3 Walked Away: Sight looked back. Lips licked ,,(Fes)'' held <i>her</i> stare, lipped ,,Call it.'' Daughter smiled and took first steps, said ,,Good morning'' to a future satisfied customer.

Fes to office. The comment: ,,...And your gum chewing solicits arrogance.'' Nods of Departure. 

All in cadence to two pieces of winter mint gum. 

The tap is a habit of time...

For stagnant routes...

For movement screams...

For the call for activity ,,<i>It's about fucking time.</i>''

To Move Forward: Fes bounces inside two door combustion machine with <i>Harmonic Bliss</i> pushed through one meter cones to alter beat of heart, drip of sweat, angle of rearview image - numb body and mind. 

It is said you should not fuck to a metronome, so the sound: a percussion of various tempos (moderato: forward): Largo, Adagio, Andantino, Presto drops of Bass.

Down shift...

Red Line

...for the need of speed.

Denial of placement (a habit to evade <i>Time</i>).

Digits tap tempos. 

Bubbles pop harmony.

Fes ejects <i>Inspiration</i> looped for two week play.

Tosses <i>Stuttered Hyper Tracks</i>. 

Indices indexed for <i>Spatial Bliss</i> beneath sheet of feather treble and bass (<i>The Honey Dews</i>). Sight scans location. Lane free of commerce. Reaches. Shuffles pop scripts, barrette, tuning fork, transceiver, disk of reverend tracks (in palm) to transducer. Play. A grin. Swirl of wrist and palm to voice(over) lifts glass soul above the clouds, pushes lips to whisper redundant tone. 
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
