<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="18" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Call it: ''<i>Pop| It| In|</i>''

A grin. Fes pushes shades - back.
 
Shaft slides slow - brake. 

Exit. 

The White Picket. The rails of steel that lead to the dock. The shipping yard strapped by the spike and the rust. The yells for and of the direction. The bang of the hammer and the nail. The lunch whistle. The calls to the port. The yards for the export. The heaven for the strays. The nocturnal lights. The train tracks. The smoke stacks. Under the viaduct. The signal - left. The mind. The tap...the tap...the tap...the tap...Fes taps left under viaduct upon a gravel road, pulls up slow, lowers tune, smiles when another is near, rolls down window to feel the fresh air and <i>see The White<i> Picket Painted Gray</i>. 

Fes at play in the field of sand. Two turns left and Fes is on the way. Home, right there (ocean view). Windows of glass and screen. Light wood frame. Redwood for base. Fes helped pour the cement pillars by transmitting sound. 

Lights dim before garage door - jammed. Ignition - off. Fes shoves open door, lifts over fallen gray picket to sand-grass lawn, <i>snaps</i> neck, <i>sees</i> over shoulder. 

<i>...Inhale.</i>

Exhale... 

<i>To fill base...</i>

Covet the hollow for the shallow.

<i>To Play.</i>

A vacancy in the span of the time...

<i>To Hide:</i>

Family - mom Mary <i>father</i> - is where Fes slows tempo. Screams of ,,How much?'' echo. Pitch swages with creak of Oak Door. Sun beams blind. Pack on shoulder. Key in pocket.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

