<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="27" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mary flows hall of empty frames and nailed images. Mary's wind-wake pushes free <i>Image of Nascent Mary</i> before beach house hidden by sea shells. <i>Image of Nascent</i> <i>Mary</i> brushes site, <i>Mary's 1st Experience of Motion</i>, subtitled <i>With A Unicycle</i> (BLOCKS upon flower petals before the manor <i>Over the Vapor of Valley</i>). <i>Mary's 1st Experience of Motion</i> tips drawing <i>Mountains and Pien</i> of the valley of green during summer time: A hill of grass; Mom in a dress; Mary below; Sun flower upon palm. Drawing tops portrait <i>Sun Dress and Tropic Sun</i>. <i>Sun Dress and Tropic Sun</i> covers <i>Snow Cabin of Alpine</i>: Snow up to Mary's ripe waist; Pink cap over a smooth fluff; Snow boots and mittens. Mary mittens door of hall closet, whispers ,,<i>Blue coat and yellow shoes</i>,'' palm clears the dust, sets blue coat and yellow shoes on the floor near the site of Mary, the idol of metropolis soundhall (nameless masks pass notes). Mary muffles sight of sound <i>Mary In Ivy Cap and Gown</i>. Faded site, barriers ''<i>Fes.</i> You recount this...(wind taps hip)...Was this Oxford, Yale or Princeton?''

Mary smiles, flows to site of analog frequencies: Fes folds frequent analog modulated forces, draws a cursive <i>L</i> (force on left), slides force closer to right (force on right), spins back left (force on left), slides force under left force and pushes force under base, stands - staves apart - left force draws a cursive <i>L</i> (force on right), slides force closer to left (force on left), spins back to right (force on right), slides force under right force and pushes right force under bass, stands - staves apart - right force draws a cursive <i>L</i> (force on left), slides force right closer to right (force on right), spins forward to left...tosses force into 

Mary smiles at analog modulated slides (anti-clockwise box (two second intervals between the two analog modulated forces bass and treble)).
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

