<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="30" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Fes points to keys, shakes ,,<Yes>, have the pick-up. I shall pick it up tomorrow. Mary may guide Steve's Old Machine. I shall have another guide.''
 
Mom checks the reflection's mask, bow, collar and lenses in the mirror hung over the stove by (etched) <i>Portrait of Mary and Mother</i>.

Call it: ''<i>The Length of Static</i>''

,,<i>I need a sabbatical. I need to tap,</i>'' whispers mom ''<i>I need to connect with the sight</i>.''

Fes gives mom a paper note stuck to the stove ,,The site. It is here,'' points to the digits pinned to wall hall map of metropolis, flows to it, flows from it, wiggles the digits. 

Mom kisses Fes, brushes Fes's digits with palm, folds Fes's digits ,,Thanks, Fes.''

,,<i>That was cryptic</i>,'' whispers Fes, pivots to sofa, arranges the pillows, the sets of three indices.

,,<i>Yo</i>u suppose?'' wisps mom.

Fes supposes. Mom wraps coat and scarf. Fes gives mom the supposition labeled with red words: The Theory of Amplitude. Points and says ,,What think?''

Mom smiles ,,It is cryptic,'' shakes and pulls back shroud ''Listen. Fes.''

(:Fes:) ,,Yes, I will.''

Mary enters room. Pigtail dances over shoulders. Smell of pink settles. Lips pu<i>rr</i> for Silence ,,<i>May</i> I <i>have</i> the keys to the crate or <i>shall I have</i> to stand on the street and <i>whisper</i> the message <i>first to have room in their crate has Mary</i>?''

Fes, searches canvas pack, gives Mary a conundrum. <i>Mother</i> 

<i>Mother</i> slaps Fes ,,CARE. (...sight of Mary) And think. With your beauty you won't have to worry about any associations.''

Mary laughs, puts conundrum in shirt pocket, traces lubricated circle.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
