<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="31" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mother <i>sees</i> Mary's sight ''If you choose to unwrap the conundrum use your mind when you read and conjecture.''

Fes laughs ,,It is the gospels for Jesus, mom.''

Sights to mom for the smile of ,,Will Jesus fuck you, Mary?'' ,,Only when I suppose (Mary's Tenor). YeS.'' Mary walks to door and points to Fes ''I suppose.''

Mom gathers canvas wrap and briefcase (knocks over two stacks of indices - Fes stiffens) - mom says ,,Fes, I am sorry,'' and says to ''Mary, Fes said you could have Steve's Old Machine.''

The sound of combustion. The shine of light. The smell of exhaust. The taste of tar. The vibration of horn. 

Fes laughs to self ,,How has it been said,'' sight to ''Mary, the only way two humans who hate are intimate with the other is when the two humans fight, fuck or dance.'' 

Mary tosses comb to couch, whips pigtail at ,,Fes. One (whips pigtail) we fight. Two (whips pigtail) they fuck. I suppose you need to dance-

-I danced last night-

-And we sung?''

,,I want you. You want to fuck?'' ,,Then we breathed.'' ,,Then we wanted to breathe <i>could you tickle me here</i>.'' ,,Are you moving?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,Was it...too...much...fun?'' ,,<i>Maybe</i>.'' ,,Maybe?'' Mary sets <i>Pose of Discontent(%)</i> ''Why?'' ,,Maybe. Maybe I supposed the supposition for <i>you</i> Speak Not so we may <i>tap</i> forever.''

Call it: ''<i>The Perpetual Tap</i>''
 
...But leave the door open to <i>see</i> the struggle. To hear the shuffle of force as mind pulls the conduit from socket: The Shock of Discourse. 

Fes pushes sofa against wall, rolls rug and tips rug in corner, pulls podium through Room with Couch and Television, through hall, upon the tile and to the sun-room.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
