<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="33" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mary's  laughter  invades  the  clash  of  cymbals  and  the exasperation of tuba. Right force kicks ''Fes!'' Body (back), legs spread (forward) ''You're thinking!'' Left force points to crouch ''I think not!''

Fes's  sight  -  red.  Palms  over  pelvis.  Joints  flow  back ,,You were watching and I knew it! How you expect us not to think!'' Fes places palms over Mary's sight ''<i>See</i> not and know not and I shall think not!''

Mary picks up a pill and a glass of water ,,Take both of these <i>and call it in the morning!</i>'' 

Fes scowls, claps, points to analog synthesizer ,,<i>It</i> will corrupt!''

Mary paces upon vinyl - windows rattle note - waves dust ,,What is here?''

,,Nothing,'' Fes waves toward piano ''Cryptic...of course you read.''

,,The notes are scribbles...(points)...I...like...this.'' 

Bell rings.

Mary exhales in waves ''((Here)), it's<i> the</i> S<i>teve</i>.''

Fes smiles, whispers ,,<i>Bitch</i>,'' shakes and cradles cone between mind and soul, walks to stoop, shuts screen door ''Yes...No...no, you listen. What is the number of trips to the beach this year? ...And what is the number of trips to the beach last year...That is what I thought...You want to go to the beach and you want someone who wants to go to the beach with- ...you can only blame yourself...maybe...maybe...if you know not you will be telling the tale of Mike  and  Steve, a pair of stones.''  Dial  mixed  for  time, shines on wrist, reflects red and blue (yellow in the sight). Fes squints, ashes and sets pose for reply. Fes shakes <No> while digit taps pace ''How many times? Four? Maybe two? Would once be enough...No...Yes, Mary's here...yes...one tap...'' Fes opens screen door.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
