<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="37" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mary dips bread into the tomato soup ,,Well...you dive in?''

,,I was not I.'' 

,,Were we <i>seen</i> with the other?''

Fes remembers: Lights over the Mezzanine, Lights over the Balcony, Lights in the Mirrored Room, Lights in the Dinning Room, the other ,,<No>, we were <i>seen</i> not (uncovers receiver). Steve, Mary needs me to braid so I shall <i>see</i> you again when you arrive with Mike. Bye.''

Fes sits on sofa, waves for Mary and says ''What time is it?''

Mary shrugs ,,I know not.''

,,Good, now sit...thank you...and hold still,'' Fes yanks pigtail and softly ushers pigtail to the mirror ''<i>See,</i>'' twirling end ''You know not so it is complete. Now, I need your assistance. Will you assist me in transposing the notes to the white board?'' Fes flows around room.

,,Yes,'' Mary leads Fes to wall hall, points to white board ''There and draw the treble upon the bass.'' 

,,No.''

,,Please and I-

,,You suppose.'' 

,,Yes, I suppose,'' Mary walks from room, presses: Largo - [Off] and twists the copper wire and fastens a gold pronged plug to the copper wire to create a conduit of energy to rotate two disks. Fes covers Two ~Rotating~ Discs. Mary sets conduit upon cover of two ~rotating~ disks. Fes sets the stone tempo keys, the steel knobs, the bone dials upon glass cover of Two ~Rotating~ Discs. Mary lifts the Two ~Rotating~ Discs' glass case. Fes flows (with conduit). Boards creak with passage. Mary <i>sees</i> ''Fes, another is about to tap the door. Answer the tap. Tell the tale of our house and our wish not to <i>see</i> outside.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
