<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="40" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
what I think I want but am unable to express...I know... directly... maybe...indirectly...is someone else there I may speak with...Fes...Are You There?''

Patti picks up the receiver ,,Hello, Mike. This is Patti.''

Fes <i>sees</i> the action of the screen latch - up, waves to Mary, who departs with Silence, so Fes taps. Patti <i>sees</i> Fes place palm over mouth and whisper ,,<i>Press the button</i>.''

Patti presses the button and Mike's voice vibrates house: ,,||I WANT NOT TO LEAD YOU BUT|....I'M SEARCHING FOR|| (Patti turns knob down/) another who wishes for the other more than-

-Turn off the Mike. We will speak soon.''

,,'O'kay!''

Repsires ,,Now press the transmitter's off button and call your whore Steve! Steve will be your needs.''

...Static...

Patti presses off and throws receiver down the hall ,,The Mike sounds...too...much...fun.''

Fes points to latch and presses palms together in front of form and lips the word ,,<P><L><E><A><S><E>.''

Patti laughs, rubs thighs (spreads redolence) ,,Are you sure you want to come inside?'' Latch - lifted. 

Wind catches. Door - BANG!!! ...Screen falls...

Fes slides inside ,,Thank you. I would be indebted to you if would perform the act of getting and giving me the note stuck to the stove.'' 

Patti exhales mirth, swallows, gets the note and waves the note afore ,,Fes, what is this?'' Holds note afore Fes. 

,,A note from the parents.''

,,They are?''

,,They exist.''

,,No, a statement. They are <i>fun</i>.''

,,One is a phylogeneticist. Other a retired colonel who
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

