<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="42" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Call it: ''<i>Why is the Sky Blue?</i>''

Door opens. Lights shock (an electric discharge (outside)) and Mary's awe ''COME INSIDE!''

,,<i>No,</i>'' whispers Fes ''<i>Not without an invitation or an acceptance of who you think you want to be tonight.</i>'' Door shut. The <i>silhouette</i> and Mary embrace. 

Fes reveals record - sneezes - closes silver case, storms to <i>silhouette</i>, speaks ''I would offer you a towel. However, I am afraid it would require effort, so please stand here until the excess moisture within your clothing and upon your frame dries for I wish not for Mary's material to become tainted with your essence and image to become clouded by your inability to remember your proper name.''

,,It's Leah,'' Lisa says.

,,Alone and full of self. Or is full of self and alone.''

Cat Call from Across Gravel Way ,,YES, That's how you come unto us!''

Fes visors sight with palm. Mary peers out window.

Patti's site of Mary. Mary smiles, points to Fes. Mary whispers to Leah ,,<i>I told Fes our little secret</i>.''

,,Little!'' says Fes, runs palms over flesh, exhales, inhales, snorts ''Little.''

They share a laugh under cover of wrists ,,Oh, well I suppose that makes you a whore.'' 

Mary smiles ,,Yes, (walks away) I am.''

Fes walks to sheet, draws staves upon wall. Treble upon Bass ,,And where shall I drop the silhouette, Leah?'' Back to Lisa, marker balances afore upon digits. Fes swages. 

Lisa (spreads blonde to express it. Tastes new but fades to old after first swallow - Sun and Beach Highlights (Tamed by aloe) - falls in layers over flesh when whipped back to lighten taste, melts in mouth) glides to piano, spreads over keys, drips upon peddles...<i>Chopsticks</i>?
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

