<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="45" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Steve lowers tone, sips water, <i>sees</i> through window ,,Is Leah encapsulated sound?''

Fes smiles - ((laugh)) echoes down hall - stops - leans (back), palms upon joints ,,Yes, Leah is a played note.''

Steve laughs with sight wide ,,Yes..You..Too..''

The leaves - quiet. The wind - stagnant. The grass - wet. The dirt...Too many words of flesh movement and not enough fluid action. Sight searches for the other subject to focus upon. The arrangement of the pictures upon the tree. The indices upon the couch. The weather. The Or?

Fes taps upon the naked wrist ,,What time is it?''

,,Ten:forty-five,'' Patti flows by Fes, redolence clouds blinking lights above Steve, inhibits Silence to purr, blinks with lashes five times ''Fes. When. Will. Mike. Arrive?'' 

Fes...inhales. Fes exhales... ,,Any time I suppose. The Steve and Mike are like stone because they are solid, hard...to get moving and used to build the stone dial.''

,,And you?''

,,Solidity, movement or the other's time?''

,,Solidity and movement.''

,,More than I want to admit,'' Fes flows by Patti, brushes Patti's cloud, whispers ''<i>Thank you</i>''...rests upon table.

Patti smiles, runs dew up Fes's stave ,,And the other's time?''

,,Oh, I exist for me. But if I were asked to be cast as a monument of we.'' Arms spread. Feet crossed. Fes smiles, shrugs ''Who would not want to be cast as a monument?''

,,I wouldn't. I want to cast time.''

An Uncomfortable Silence|......... Wills form base and will the other not to accept minds' desire to silence dialog of existence and purr of instinct, movement and near-naked flesh for sight, smell and taste of flesh. The reply of Yes. The 4-play dance. The sex. The orgasm. The euphoria.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
