<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="49" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Sara waves: <Thanks>. Guides the others to sit. Feed. Clean. Conducts the others to tell the tale of thanks for the other's respect. Sings hymn of <i>Forget Not, </i>Give The Others Respect From The Source of Respect Given To Mother.

...The Electric Discharge...

Laughter: ,,The line is not of the song?'' ,,You record the record too much?'' 

Volume low. Fes stretches (back), gives a peach to ,,Sara, how much time have you known Simon?'' ,,Time enough to cast you.'' ,,Simon says and Simon lies.'' ,,Yes, Simon casts illusions.'' Leah's voice from afar ,,<i>Fes</i>, I will we go. <i>The other</i>...is waiting for you at the door.'' ,,What time is it?'' ,,<i>Time to</i> go.'' ,,Yes. Who is guiding?'' ,,Steve and I.'' ,,I will you guide.'' ,,What is my position?'' ,,Front or Back?'' ,,You choose.'' ,,Sara?'' ,,Front.'' ,,Simon?'' ,,Back.'' ,,Thank you. What time is it?'' ,,Nine:fifty-one.'' ,,It is ten:fifty-two.''

Fes whispers ,,<i>Thank you</i>, Sara,'' smiles ''Mike, Mary called. Wished to speak with you. However, I want not to get hit by the stones, so I told Mary you said `hi'. Mary said `hi is good' ...but Mary prefers hello. Oh, Sara and Simon. If you will you to smoke we want you outside. I want not the smell to float and stain inside.''

Sara -n- Simon with fire -n- fuel to lawn. Leah, Mike and Steve band. Patti walks hardwood bowl to basin, slides to counter, pulls beaker from envelope purse, flows to Fes, dangles beaker afore sight ,,I won't tell Mary.'' Fes grins.

The Outside Crowd - returns inside.

Steve's laugh ((echoes)) as the band steps into Couch -n- Television Room ,,So Fes, you want to tap Sara.''

Fes skips stanza ,,Tap. You say `Tap'?'' ...forces a blush. Blush for ''Sara, I have intentions of wanting to fuck the other''...site to...''Mike, I will the stones sting your ass for I will you are the target. Please, close the screen. 
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
