<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="54" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Liripipe - slapped. Door - shut...Hall - echoes. Hard Floor - creaks. Bed - squeaks...Sheets - tossed. Cloths - stripped. Shelves - cleared. ''Where is the fescue?'' (Rinforzando(every eight seconds...then four!)). Fes files sheets of notes and staffs, forms, crates stacked under window's seal. Fes snuffs flame of candle and shuts window, proofs image before mirror. Door - locked. Key in pocket. Taps echo from hall to kitchen. Pack - tossed (indexed). Strap drawn, over shoulder. Fes stands before all ''Where is the fescue? It is a stave with the width of a thumb.''

Patti struts to and points to record ,,I know not...what you expressing on tonight?''

Fes wipes sweat, smiles, taps hardwood floor ,,Sympathy for Steven,'' spreads to make a statement the question ''You have the silk?'' 

Steve closes the trunk, activates the bell. The door opens with the squeaks. The silk unrolls upon the hardwood floor. ''Thank you, Steve. Mike, please shear.''

Mike licks tip. Taps digit on shear's edge. Folds silk. Slices silk ,,The other theorem for your postulate?''

Fes flows to Simon and leans ,,Yes,'' turns with arms wide ''Sara, you competent with digits?''

Sara laughs, stretches upon couch ,,Yes. Are you?''

Smiles -n- Laughter hidden behind palms (Mike and Steve wiggle digits). Leah flows from room, sonus trails ,,Sara, Fes knows not of probability and still counts you a mark upon the headboard even if the obvious method is applied. (Turns) Your use of arithmetics to sing the notes that compose your postulates is not good, Fes.''

,,Counting Digits tapped you.''

Leah pops^ back ,,Need a little thought. YOU <i>hap</i>pen to have the only digit near that I <i> c o u l d t a p u p o n</i>.''

Fes shakes form, tumbles to pot of cherries -n- leaves
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
