<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="58" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
...places it in pack, wanders outside to Steve -n- Mike.

Call it: ''Yet To Call''

Mike exhales ,,<i>W</i>orry not,'' clears throat, spits, says to <i>Fes</i> ''Maybe it taps and maybe it taps not.'' 

,,Maybe the other I is fighting with <i>her</i> tonight,'' inhales Steve, shakes, taps door of Steve's New Machine, peers through passenger window, <i>sees</i> to Mike, who <i>sees</i> to Fes, smiles, exhales... ,,Maybe the other is fucking <i>her</i> tonight.'' Steve sits within ,,Maybe <i>her</i> dance is too lascive for your purity...or purity (laughs, shuts door, flips switch - unlocks doors). Maybe <i>her</i> form is merry and tongue deep in pussy right now. Maybe <i>her</i> form is frank and mouth too full of dick to call (slides key into ignition, twists key).'' 

Mike waves for Sara to <~<i>go</i>~> and for ,,~Fes~.''

,,Yes, Mike.''

Slaps Fes ,,We get in. We GO!''

...<i>metronome blue bleep bling</i>... 

Fes presses the Little Green G'O' Button.

,,<i>When was the last time we called it?</i>''

,,It has been a tap and a half.''

,,<i>A tap and a half or was it two taps of time?</i>''

,,Both.''

,,<i>Two taps of time we dance.</i>''

,,Yes.''

,,<i>We dance with the other a tap and a half.</i>''

,,Yes, we show our site.''

,,<i>The site of faith?</i>''

,,The Site of Faith is the sight that discourses the Sight of We cite our site of three sights.''

,,<i>What three sights?</i>''

,,Maybe we, <i>you and I</i>, <i>see</i> I. Maybe we, <i>you and I</i>, <i>see</i> you. Maybe we, <i>you and I</i>, <i>you and I see the other</i>.''

,,<i>What thee want when we </i>see the other?''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
