<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="10" authors="Kalab J. Oster">





<i>There was a girl.</i>

<i>A girl who never liked the image from the mirror.</i>

<i>The image was too skinny, too fat, too tall, too short or too uneven.</i>

<i>The image ate, fasted, slouched, stretched and leaned. The image read articles and hung the pictures around the mirror so one morning the image could see a girl say ,,I will never be beautiful.''</i>

<i>A girl withdrew. Found solace with the others the image knew. Those images caste on screen and page. Lived beneath their shade. To be them if only for a day. The image thought.</i> Then maybe someone would listen for what I say<i>.</i>

<i>...But there are never shadows center stage...</i>

<i>...Lost in the glitter of night the stare...</i>

<i>The image awoke during the dawn, before the image of the mirror, to see what the world could not bare. A portrait neither withered nor warped and, if so, only because of their ridicule and unwillingness to care.</i>

<i>A girl awoke. The sun at center stage. The mirror a blinding page. A girl whispered to hear a woman say ''So what if I am never what they want to see. I am as beautiful as a human could be.''</i>

<i>The mirror bare - cracked. The Frame of Pictures Pages stacked, set for the trash, beneath the stairs.</i>

<i>There was a woman.</i>

<i>A woman who was out at night to muse.</i>

<i>A muse to cool the warm wind of hades. A muse contained by a shroud to feel faded echoes of a phase.</i>

<i>A woman flowed to a muse's epicenter. The fanatics that surround were told to remain still. A woman entered. A woman was told to ponder the muse at will for the muse may feel. The muse looked up unto the images of the stars in the sky with the smile of ''Goodbye.''</i>
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
