<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="12" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
<i>call it ''</i>Oh my<i>...'' whispered the muse for the sight of it.</i>

<i>Sight followed the force. It strayed to the preacher-over-podium casting emotional discourse. Its notes rubbed the mind. Its body flowed in the wave. It sung the first chirp of the night. No reply ( No echo ). No longer in the cave. People pointed, spread their arms to eclipse the rising sun then let echo sight. To feel the mass of ,,Too much fun''...And then there was the Burn-off of Night.</i>

<i>The crowd set forth a psalm. It spread arms to bare wrist and palm. It relaxed its frame. The crowd cried when it looked up without shame. After the emotion warmed with inalts. It unwrapped so the crowd could see faults.</i>

<i>,,</i>Go!<i>''</i>

<i>The dawn of light.</i>

<i>Heat waves baptized the ocean of minds that danced above the stile. Their mass to the rise of tempo. Their minds the puppeteers. A shallow bass their only fear. The echo of congo drums rapping to their clap. It slid the length of the scales, tipped its thorn cap.</i>

<i>''</i>GO.<i>''</i>

<i>Crowd inhaled...cheered surfeit intensity: A sub-sonic wave of thunder and - gathered by the collective of damned repression - sinuating waves of simplex sound struck a cloud. Rain fell from the sky. Acute angles. Obtuse degrees. One arm strung twine to tips of feet. Spine: horizontal, neck to tail, impervious to limb and joint to snap, mouth to whisper and whistle ''</i>Go!<i>''</i>

<i>Sight closed. The muse numb. Lungs contracted. Mind spun. The crowd cheered the coming of the sun. The dawn of light. The break of silence and dim of sight.</i>

<i>The ethereal mist spread clear.</i>

<i>''</i>GO!<i>''</i>

<i>A span of                            A tremor of</i>
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
