<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="13" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
<i>''||</i>GO||!<i>''</i>

<i>It spread its rays of sun light. There was hark from above for the smell of a lighting strike. The taste of mildew given by the night. To bathe in its heat now they no longer have sight.</i>

<i>They shook thunder, clapped lighting, called for rain with tap of foot and hand, a storm of sonus and the earth began to hymn...it to glow....the silk of illusion to fall...reveal its corporeal shape.</i>

<i>The woman grinned when it looked upon.</i>

<i>The woman smiled when it blurred ''</i>Too much fun.<i>''</i>

<i>The woman's smile of ,,If you asked I would look into the sun. Stare until you said stop. (...lick of ) But I need to know before I look. (...exhale of) I need to know what to call it so you know where we're going?''</i>

<i>...and you whispered</i> ''I know not.''

Call it: ''<i>Epoche</i>''

...Gray wisps beneath its zenith...

<i>Ripples of gold reflected true. Amongst The Blue.</i>

Silent strings of flocks. Toward the docks.

<i>Distant from the drip of exhaust. The Scream</i>: 

,,Move the fuck<i>in</i> machine.''

An applause of horns and an ensemble of engines' roar trapped within concrete walls decorated by the vine, the door, the hood and the heavens above. Pleas for eternal transmission throttled by ideals, governed by sermons of what is real - lost echoes.

Amongst the mirage of the horizon.

Ripples of Red reflect Gold.

Gray wisps beneath its set.

Signals right.

Turn Left:

Tap, Tap, Tap, Tap...
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
