<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="14" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
It is more of a snap than a tap when gum is in Fes's mouth. Jaw pulses and tongue passes the gum from one side to the other side of the mouth with a parted lip to fume mint when attitude runs the beat of gums and teeth.

The gum is a habit Fes has tried to quit.

Fes considers the gum a social indignity, a distraction during sexually evasive conversation...and the gum floats around. But the breath with gum is pleasant (some say the breath enlightens the mind) and the gum sets pace while Fes works, reads and | or talks to the phonic cone.


,,The gum solicits arrogance.'' The utterance under wheeze of nose from Manager Jeff in Manager Jeff's Office after noon consumers. During dawn consumers Jeff held clip board with finger and palm, legs spread, a stain on tie.

Fes, akimbo, tapped white illusion silk shipped express for opera company.

Jeff displayed various shades of red with face (sweat beads) and fist, knuckles white, pounded <i>Fall Leaves</i> catalog for punctuation ''-Why. Are. These. Holes. Here.''

Fes, tired, tapped the mouth ,,Hmmmm... These... Holes... Here...''

Fes knew. Fes knew the order was to size. Fes knew Manager Jeff would not allow Fes to take a yard free of charge.

So Fes removed illusion silk between red and green cotton sheets stocked for rush, crafty housemaids love home made stockings, always a good image, better than the image of Fes, with silk over back, paused at courtesy phonic cone to press friends to fulfill the request of ''Yes, yes, by the catalogs and burn it after you have unrolled it...yes...yes...It is for <i>her.</i>''

Friends entered scene at ten:fourteen. 

Manager Jeff tore dilated sight from monitor at ten: 
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
