<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="16" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Fes, tired, tapped mouth ,,Hmmmm...These...Holes...He<i>re</i>. I looked and I was not displaying red and green (tongue across teeth, arms behind back, chin tilted - down).''

Jeff teetered on heels, dilated pupils followed, the blood vessel about to burst, the mouth said ,,This is an unexcusable occurrence. <i>See</i> Jeff, in the office, before you leave.''

Fist pounded paper. The Punctuation of Departure. In chime with Child Dissonance. The resonance of Customer Number Three in battle with baby over knotted hair: A Call for Customer Service.

Another stick of the gum soft in the mouth. 

Customer Number Three said ,,...the hot, pink, fabric by the yellow ducks complements blush and at home some hot, pink, bows were discovered under bed and I think they'd go great with blush and new hairdo.''

Fes smiled, stepped back ,,It is not for your daughter?'' blew a bubble, cracked air, looked behind (Jeff in office) back to <i>Her</i> Number Three in model pose before mirror. 

Hot pink wrapped around hips ,,What you think?''

Fes tapped, saw <i>her</i> sight - asked ,,You care if I?'' <i>Her</i> shake <NO>. Fes site'd <i>her</i> up and down ''Mmmmm maybe not the hot pink. You want <i>her</i> to be a woman. It complements not <i>her</i> mother's natural beauty. Have you tried forest green or maple brown...translucent?''

<i>Her</i> daughter, silent.

Fresh mint fumed forth in rhythmic force to help <i>Her</i> Number (#) Three (3) to smile, laugh and agree. All with two winks, a story of <i>her</i> lover, a tear streaked stare, a palm-held walk to Forest of Fabrics, a `small' Joke of Manager Jeffrey.

<i>Her</i> #3 smiled, slid Fes <i>her</i> name and number, rubbed Fes's ring finger-digit during exchange. Fes replied with digits for <i>her</i> to call to collect <i>her</i> twenty dollar change.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

