<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="20" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Call it: ''<i>Idiosyncratic</i>''

Nascent Being. Entwined. Over Shoulder Mischief. Palm Impressions Under Cover of The Cloth. Lap on Lap (Motion Against Palm). Face Paint Licked...Away. Too Dark. Silence. Buttons of Trousers Pulled. Belt Tightened. Released. Buttons Pop Off. Motion: Curtains sway to bounce of bed. A moan. A squeal. Yes. Palm over mouth. Air sucked between fingers. A bite. Teeth pinch. Flesh - held. Nascent Being leaps up, pulls garments, tightens rope, points to palm - screams|hollers: ,,THAT FUCKING HURT.'' ...<i>Her</i> laugh of ,,The Price of Submission.'' Door opened. <i>Her</i> midnight blouse, stained by excitement, floats. <i>Her</i> body leans against pillar, sits, reveals locket. <i>Her</i> finger fondles a necklace of innocence, opens locket to show nascent youth and mother, a contemporary image, an heirloom of <i>Time</i>, displayed if Nascent Being obeys.

Across Gravel Way Nascent Being begs from door ,,I'm sorry. You caught me by surprise. Forgive me, please.''

,,<i>Sorry</i>,'' Fes bites digits, smiles, spits, wraps gum, puts 
wrap in pack, takes out smoke.

,,You were going to quit,'' Mary opens the door.

,,I was but I need to keep pace...want one?''

,,Yes.''

,,Another walk home.''

,,I had them drop me off at the viaduct. Needed to clear the air.''

,,Another one of those days?''

,,I played innocent today. Well, it seemed innocent but when we rehearse the director positions my body as an example and says it is for the part. Acts as if it is my only role.''

,,I am not shocked,'' Fes blows a trail of smoke.

,,I suppose.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
