<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="21" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Across Gravel Way: The Nascent Being behind begs to <i>her</i> shadow. 

Fes ashes ,,Too many attempts to sing your way in?''

Mary pulls back for a pony tail, wipes ashes from skirt, straightens jacket ,,May I sit?''

Fes...inhales, brushes step and leans against the rail, <i>sees</i> Mary above, exhales... ,,Yes, you may.''

,,Thanks.''

,,Another one of those days?''

,,Yes. I suppose I played naïve today.''

,,Too much of the other's creation?''

,,I suppose.''

,,What were we wearing?''

,,Turtle neck, black, maybe navy blue, I care not - Fes.''

,,And?''

,,And maybe pleated pants, socks and-

-black shoes-

-Yes.''

Through screen (door): ,,Maybe either one of you shut the door?''

,,Yes...mother,'' says Mary, leans back and swoons door shut. It clicks closed. A muffled ,,Thank you, dear.''

,,Continue, please,'' Fes smothers smoke, grins for another, lights under palm, <i>sees</i> to Mary, exhales.

A cough ,,I sung a little, was told to get tea...where's your smoke?''

,,What?'' Fes jitters, sight on Mary (limbs lost in Fes's canvas pack). ,,Smoke.'' ,,At the bottom.'' ,,What's this?'' ,,A flyer.'' ,,Good.'' ,,Thanks!'' ,,You create it?'' ,,Yes!'' ,,The Hour of Fun?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,That discoursed.'' ,,How?'' ,,Why not call it `Too much fun'?'' ,,Because it could be said to ridicule. Too...Much...Fun.''

,,That was weird. I never felt weird until today.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
