<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="22" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
,,You remember to breathe?'' says Fes, stands to brush the ash, remnants of smoke, from trousers and pullover. A thought of rain. No clouds in the blue sky. Echoes of Skeletons locked in the cellar by the wine and Instances of Glory sung in stories of collegiate seasons at the party where I thought I met the <i>her</i>, the distance we once danced, refract the clouds Across Gravel Way. Fes lowers to step, folds self to witness the storm ''So what is on the index of tonight?''

,,Whatever dreams may come.''

Fes flicks smoke to lawn ,,Hold not your breath for when you wake you will meet reality.''

Mary casts a glare of deceit, straightens posture ,,If I suppose yes.''

Fes points index Across Gravel Way <The Nascent Being at Play Across Gravel Way> ,,No dreams supposed - TONIGHT!'' flicks Mary's smoke Across Gravel Way.

Thighs on shoulders.

Tongue between the moisture.

The wet spot.

Feet quiver. 

Hands pull at grass.

Hyperventilation.

A purr

...<i>her</i> moan. 

Call it: ''<i>The Smell of Release</i>''

Fes opens door, <i>sees</i> something that resembles mom (passed unconscious by the toxin), talks of another, walks to bedroom with tele-vision-speak shouting at the sun, calling for the shades, echoes sight: <The Father Weeping> ,,What happened to my sun?'' exhales flame release, shuts door of room with bed, a collage of creation: Schematics, outlines, indicia, equations, notes, charts, graphs, lines, 
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
