<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="23" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
plots, staves spread over floor during the Rain of Homo Sapien Response forsaken with too many thumbs and too many abstract theories and not enough time to create. Where to start? The symphony? Or the sculpture? Or the release of insecurity upon the other's emotional being?

Fes clears a site before the mirror and places the pose. An innocent site before interaction with <i>her</i>. A grin slowly grows to a smile while in <i>her</i> sight. 

Fes learned the blush, the cry, the sob and the swelling of sight during emotional dialog with <i>her</i>. Sometimes sight flushed red and a tear would drop to floor with emotional dialog of life with <i>her</i>.

Sight lost upon wardrobe and ware for celebrations but then again everything is a celebration. The poetry of dawn was never read by Fes, who prescribes to tele-vision-mom ,,Turn it off (tells Fes to ,,Shut the door'').'' ''Yes, mom.''

Fes mumbles index of attire under exhale ''<i>Chaperon,</i> <i>Liripipe,</i> pantaloons<i>...</i>'' strikes flint and steel to light the wick to melt the ink, dips, to write: Mark - Chapter >Ten Twenty-Three<. A time for release during the months of cum (come) over in(to) my kingdom and beat the drums. 

Fes knows the drums echo symbolism but the sound fades from the stream of subconscious existence that plays for Fes's sight (too loud) so Fes lowers to the Abyss, <i>Under Too Many Waves of Distress</i>. In the Abyss Fes laughs and Fes is baptized. Sings to phonic cone and form is blessed. Prays for will to flip the switch, to turn up (the dew) volume for mind to hymn count of Bass Ten so Soul exists. Fes <i>snap</i>s count. Soul snaps cadence of metronome bling Zero - <i>snap</i> - One - <i>snap</i> - Two - <i>snap</i> - Three - <i>snap</i> - Four - <i>snap</i> - Five - <i>snap</i> -Six - <i>snap</i> - Seven - <i>snap</i> - Eight - <i>snap</i> - Nine - <i>snap</i>. Mind drums bass two...

Fes, upon bed, exhales... ''<i>What time is it</i>?'' Fes taps
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
