<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="24" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
time, taps base of lamp, taps headboard, taps theorems, traces theorems scribed upon 'head'board to invoke the <i>muse</i> to sit on the goose feathered pillows and silk sheets. Names in the stead of numbers. Experiments of Smell. A theorem within a postulate - whatever got them in line (drawing the thigh(')s spread of course) - to discover desire. The postulate written before the dawn. The signature envelope. The seal dry. The name on the flap. <i>X</i>. <i>X</i> The equation. The mark. <i>Her</i> sweet stain. Fes, on floor, inhales.

Call it: ''<i>Timed by the Color of Hair</i>''

Before hindsight reflects too many sexually-explicit images provoking the need for a physical altercation with self, mom's muffled voice (captive beneath a wailing trumpet and a pounding piano) screams for

,,<i>Fes</i>.''

Fes exhales, swings...presses: [Stop].

A voice invades ,,Fes, is that your new machine?!''

Mother says to Mary ,,Silence,'' and ''Fes, lower the sound.'' 

Mary yells, stomps upon hardwood ,,YES, m o t h e r.''

,,Yes.'' ((Fes))

,,Open the door.''

,,...''

,,Thank you. It was locked.''

,,Yes.'' Mary <i>sees</i> Fes smile:) ''It is Steve's old machine.''

,,May I?''

,,Maybe.''

,,Yes...Oh,'' Mary unfastens and shakes pony tails, twirls their ends, ends flow upon the frame of door. Florescent fish tank light illuminates. Image cast on wall: A Pose of Impatience(:) arms fold, digit taps treble, foot taps bass...Mary, snaps digits, poses (:)''Maybe?'' ,,Yes, Mary.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

