<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="25" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
,,The old machine?''

,,The tails.''

The walk to bed. Mary on bed. Fes on chair. Loop it. End over end. Knots over knots, a spin of three, rule of thumb and an incessant curve. It's worked before. Some move called <i>Pastiche</i>. Mary won a golden statue. Said the golden statue was shiny, but waste of raw materials. Fes told Mary to accept the golden statue to pay respect to the system. What had Fes thought? Fes knows not but knows the braid is live, so no questions of morals or creation may slight perfection. Think not. Move. A note for a rainy day. Never know what they say, what they feel or what is their name? On a rainy day... ,,Fes!''

,,Sorry, I was recounting the postulates. Tied the knot. A Frayed Note.''

,,You suppose, <i>Fes</i>.''

,,Sorry. We <i>needs </i>water.''

Mary twirls wind blown tails. Fes stomps the floor to gather the comb, the brush and the two silk bows from the uppercase above the sink. Mary blows tails. Tails float before sight, unties note, combs note loose. Fes, upon the bed, counts the strokes.

Mary <i>inhales</i>.

Fes exhales.

Mary sighs ,,Should I take a mask?''

Fes inhales. Shakes <no>.

''Why?''

Fes exhales... ,,I know not...maybe...maybe a mask will improve the entertainment of the evening? We could use your...'' Fes pulls back, sprays ''They like to yank it.''

Mary smiles, thinks of tails and dicks, laughs (when asked to describe), tells ,,They hang there with no character. So pull it to one side - Pigtail.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
