<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="26" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Fes shakes, licks plateau of pigtail fluff ,,Like this!''

,,<i>Fuck</i>, Fes!''

,,Know not?''

,,<i>Yes</i>, yes, <i>I suppose</i>, I am naïve today.''

,,Like this?''

,,Y<i>es</i>.''

,,How <i>feels</i> it?''

,,G<i>ood</i>.''

,,I know. <i>How good</i>?''

,,<i>May</i>be| <i>Too</i>| <i>Much</i>| - <i>Fuck</i>, Fes!''

Fes taps fluff ,,Somebody won't be wearing white.''

Pigtail slumps ,,Or a tuxedo. Who says I need to get married? Thanks!''

,,Yes, I suppose the minds of those that surround could wage a little to the left and a little to the right? Focus on the issues and allow you to wear what pleases you.''

Mary blows pigtail from sight ,,I suppose.''

Transmitter cones on. Volume up.

Mary pauses near receiver cone, smiles. 

Fes tucks sheets, takes pillows from hardwood floor, places pillows before hardwood headboard ,,...What?''

Mary wisps transmitter cone from ,,<i>Fes</i>, <i>the Steve</i> echoes from the receiver cone and wants to hear the sound.''

,,Tell<i> the Steve</i> I am listening to the Mike.''

Mary lips <...F...E...S?>

Takes off head cones ,,Mary?''

,,What shall we wear?''

,,Maybe the red dress...no the other, the one from outside, next to the swing, hanging on the line.''

,,Red.''

,,Yes, red. It complements the tale and the pigtail fluff. Expresses your mind's control of our desires.''

Call it: ''<i>A Reason for Nuclear Research</i>''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
