<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="29" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Yes, I promise. Steve...Yes. I will be good...bye.''

Phonic Cones swing upon switch.

Fes swoons closet door open ''What was I thinking?''

Mary's echo of ,,About the Steve's Site.''

,,Which the size of sight compensates. I have been told the Steve (:Smiles wide:) is the sight. Oh, yes, that is right. I am in it for the sight, thanks Mary.''

Fes takes Silence from crate, throws 45 upon table, points to door, relaxes elliptical needle, holds receiver against phonic cone, pops bubble to bass, slippers rub with treble: Two Peas in a Pod (one happy while the other sad). The flower cone bell rings (from the other), services for undisclosed parties. It could be the system. Who knows these days who calls? The rings of the night. The stones cast Across Gravel Way...And then there is Silence. The wind. The ocean breeze. 

Fes, with the building of solitude, exhales ''A foundation exists until someone feels a need to ruin the monument with illusions,'' departs for water to rid mind of sight. 

Silence in grasp, Fes lowers, sips, dries, twists, slides hall, closes closet door, flows to Room of Blue Glow and Hypnotized Mom, lays Silence near mom, says ''It is the time.''

Mom raises head from the lap of pillows ,,Father called.'' Fes shakes <YES> (up and down). Mom props upon elbows, purrs for Silence ''Yes, well, I am going to pick up Listen (stretches, searches for the lenses). I'll take Listen to the valley. Headin' out after.''

The pair with sight wide <i>see</i> to the other and :) (smile). The other speaks in unison ,,<i>See</i> you on the fourth.''

,,Yes,'' says the other, who points to switch board and head cones ''Listen and I will not call if we hear the reverb of sound.'' The other <i>sees</i> Fes nod...moves (forward).
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
