<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="32" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mary flows to the deck of the sun-room, <i>sees</i> Fes, wipes flesh, <i>sees</i> the stone dial, whispers ,,<i>Die Luftfeuchtigkeit</i>''

Their sights blind to <i>see</i> sound. Fes sounds ,,I know not why we are here?'' and Mary's ces echo of ,,Care not. We shall move if we want here not (pigtail flips...sunset caught in loop).''

Mary's ass upon piano, elbows upon knees, palms clasp, toes tickle keys (a serenade), sight upon Fes.

Fes pushes lamp and coffee table, pulls coffee table toward Electric Phonetic Cone, lifts tables, places tables upon piano, taps upon wall ,,Go from the sun-room.'' ,,Why?'' ,,Go from the sun-room.'' ,,No.'' ,,Close sight. I want you to <i>see not</i>.'' (and Mary <i>sees</i>) ,,I'm open.'' ,,Am I getting it?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,Is it good?'' ,,It is the performance.'' ,,Is it good?'' Mary g<i>i</i>ggl<i>e</i>s ,,Y<i>e</i>s...<i>i</i>t <i>i</i>s.'' ,,How good?'' ,,It is too...much...fun.'' ...sight closed. (:Fes:) ,,No.'' ,,What?'' ,,No.'' ,,Why?'' ,,You will care.'' ,,I care not.'' ,,Are you lying?'' ,,Am I moving?'' Fes wisps ,,<i>Yes.</i>'' ,,I promise I won't care.'',,...'' ,,...'' ,,You will care.''

Mary smiles ,,You said not to <i>see</i>.'' Mary's ass descends from piano and rests between couch and Pictures of Motion Screen (White | Black Dots - silent). Fes presses Little Green ||GO|| Button: Sounds of analog synthesizer push off walls, move the lamp, rattle the window, sway the gray picket, alter the beat of heart. The Minds lost, find the flow.

Fes lifts left, pushes forward, swings force left. Left slides (forward), raises right in front of stave, bends joints, transfers force upon stave, pushes (back) with left, strolls (forward) with stave, transfers force upon left, slides (back) with stave, transfers force upon right, lifts (forward), swings right, throws stave (back), slides with right, transfers force upon stave, transfers force upon left, pivots (forward) with right, transfers weight upon right...
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
