<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="34" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mary in kitchen over tomato soup, flame and spoon bops to beat of another. Windows rattle vocal loop `It feels good'. Rum ( for tonight Marysupposes ) feels good in the veins. Mary's sight out window.

Fes raises pitch ''MARY. Steve has asked where is the Mike?'' Mary's shakes of ''<No>...yes...Bye.''

Fes removes hot plate from stove, tilts toward window ''The night is coming.''

The Shades of Night streak Across Gravel Way. 

Mary swallows pill, pushes pill down throat with water ,,I will never wear white.''

Fes smiles ,,Hmmmm, if you choose, one day, to wear white, you could wear that dress on the couch in the viewing room.'' 

Mary slides across kitchen floor, pedals back before hall. Mary tosses aside an index to uncover...a scream: ,,OH MY. Fes, it's like a long, tight, shirt.'' ,,I found it at the craft store.'' ,,Is it mine?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,It's s<i>ooo</i>... (Receiver Rings) ...Steve.'' ,,Thanks. Yes, Steve...for? No. Are you using conundrums?'' Fes laughs, taps table ''Well...'' Mary shakes head <n>. Fes covers transmitter, taps Mary's pigtail ''...Or we could call it: Issues with Acts of Kindness. Subtitled: Wants To Be Known For Acts of A Homo Sapien.'' 

Fes uncovers transmitter ''Yes...no...maybe...maybe...yes...<i>see</i> you in a few.''

...Honks of horn...

Mary and Fes pivot, both whisper, <i>laugh</i> ,,<i>((</i>Sight<i>))</i> Sight .'' They prance to crack of door. The prance rattles television - turns it on. Black | White Dots covet the myriad bass lines Mary | Fes create while pushing piano against the Windowed Wall. Mary to ,,Fes, Please turn it off.'' 

,,...But Mary...It is Steve. Mary, you know I would never ruin our monument by mounting Steve's Key Stone.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
