<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="35" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mary taps ,,T<i>he</i>|. <i>St</i>eve|.''

Call it: ''<i>Inside Outside Inside House</i>''

,,I shall...'' and flows through the sun-room, upon the lawn to the gray picket gate for the holler ''|STEVE|. Please enter over here for I am able not to open the door.'' Steve (bleaches tips, shaves (face and chest), wraps tan flesh with suit and tie. Never fastens the top button. Powders nose. Always white. Wears glasses. Vision: 20/20. Posture - straight. Body shaped like an hour (wears a girdle)), pulls upon seam, says ,,Hell'O' (emphasis on 'O') and where is Mary this evening?''

Fes opens gate and waves to ,,Steve's new machine?''

Steve blinks, spreads musk and alcohol ,,Well, I figured what the hell, I'm worth it and you guide Steve's 'O'ld Machine.'' 

,,Yes, good times, get inside. Relax. I have three more individuals to index,'' Fes closes gate, shakes and focuses above horizon. No clouds. Stars hidden by navy blue.

Inside House: Fes opens door of hall-closet, picks grass stuck between digits, pushes aside assortment of hemp and hair coats, tips rubber boots, leather sandals, flip-flops, stilettoes, loafers - <i>sneezes</i> - drags belts and bags and masks out of closet by ''Steve,'' Fes says ''What time is it?'' 

,,I know not the time,'' the Steve blinks with the bling of the flash above the stove ''Maybe it's nine. Maybe it's ten. I know not''...Steve slides transmitter from jacket, displays transmitter for all to <i>see</i> - digits dial the red glowing buttons ''Yes, may I speak with Mike...Thank...Hell'O'...'O'kay,'' - presses pause, removes receiver from jacket pocket, listens for receiver, speaks to transmitter '''O'kay...Yes, Mike...I will be there...n'O' problem...Yes...'O'kay.''

Fes stands and hollers through hall to Steve ,,|IS IT TIME TO GO GET MIKE?|''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
