<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="36" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Steve leans over Fes's stave, grins ,,Yes...It...Is,'' frowns, stands, bats palm and pulls upon seam ''It's never the same anymore.'' 

Mary's sight: Fes. Fes shrugs.

Steve walks to door, twirls keys, strikes a pose with transmitter strapped to wrist. Transmitter twirls. Steve slides smoke from sleeve, hangs smoke from mouth ''Will return (smoke - between index and middle digit - taps beat) And Fes stop thinking you're g'O'ing to find it because you question h'O'w much you remain within another mind and not think of the other. It's not the twist of faith on The Sidewalk Where We Met and The Chapel Before It Burned epis'O'de where Little Prince Pien is A Top The Cake h'O'lding Faith and Flowers...'O'n a Sunday Afternoon.''

Fes smiles, jumps, laughs ,,'O'kay, so maybe you are right,'' waves away ''Steve, when you return I shall show you the telegraphic visions.''

Mary lights a midnight winter candle, opens a window, waves fan, flows to kitchen. Palms covet the chill of night beneath the flesh.

Fes presses play, inspects picture hall. Sound echoes in closet (IT IS STEVE!) ,,S'O' could you please tell me in a direct manner where in hell Mike lives?...I can't find IT! and I'm sick of just driving around these lifeless, gated, communities with no palms or view. FES!''

Fes covers cone, peers through hall, <i>sees</i> ,,Mary (in kitchen), when you teach the Steve to bark?!''

Mary's mouth full of wine and bread ,,Over communion. I think it was a Transmission Party. The after party. Who knows? It was just a part of the evening (fondles bread) why you ask? We were there. You recall?''

,,No,'' because <i>the sight</i> was swimming in the pool and Fes floats on water.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
