<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="38" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
,,Then what is our name?''

,,I suppose the date.''

,,And the name?''

Mary blows by ,,Yes...You suppose - <i>OUTSIDE</i>.''

Call it: ''<i>Catalytic</i>''

Fes points. Dial Turns. Bass hits. Walls ((shake)). Frames fall. Voices vibrate: ,,||THAT'S WHY IT'S MY HOUSE!||''

Mary blurs by, presses Stop...Runs ramp of hall, leaps, lands on rug, slides to door. Palm pauses before door, flips pigtail, pulls collar and necklace, cups for breath (winter mint)...turns knob of door, pulls on the knob.

,,Fes (bounces with sight focused upon spins of disk).'' 

Mary waves away the wind, twirls to silhouette ''Come inside before sand clouds the scent,'' points to rocking chair, cringes when silhouette tips stacks of indices, shoves door closed, walks to Fes's side, taps Fes.

Fes looks up:

<i>Sees</i>

...A lighting shock...

Mary shakes pigtail ''This is Patti. The one I have been telling you about the...friend who is obsessed with your movement,'' exhales...''And wants to know (with sight averted (toward the floor (near <i>Index of Recidivism</i>)) and lips taut to withhold mirth but dimples of cheeks let the mirth flow) how you move?''

Fes laughs with ,,Well (pulls back)...<i>see</i> things (points) and then I place right force forward then place right force back in right force's original position. Then place left force in and shake force.'' Fes in-line to base, spine straight, digit under flow of record ''And think not for you want not to know where you move.''

Mary turns (back), shrugs ,,We suppose.''

Patti giggles ,,You suppose?''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
