<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="39" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
,,Yes (to Sound (as Fes presses On)...an electric discharge).'' Cast light and Cast the Silhouette.

Patti (brunette cropped upon redolence. Redolence dances with breath, is <i>seen</i> under sun light - clouds of blue and yellow - flow(s) from hips. Hips flow through any room to flaunt redolence to hypnotize to provoke mind to express sense: Number Three) swirls before Fes. Lolly pop redolence upon tip. Sun dress lets redolence flow...

Fes shakes (up\ and down/), turns (90 degrees\^/) and flows toward <i>Sun Room</i> (thirty meters) to inspect <i>Sonnet </i> <i>Above</i>, speaks during departure ''Too. Much. Fun.''

,,FES!'' Patti fumes. Fumes follow <i>Fes</i> through the hall into the kitchen. Fumes pause before door. Patti weaves fumes behind ear. Fumes from floor to ''Fes. You smell?!''

,,What is there to <i>see?</i>!''

Patti leans forward and draws digit up dress ,,Lots of things.''

Fes opens screen door, slides out, closes screen door. Latch of screen locked/ ,,Show things so I may smell.''

Patti bounces up\ down/ up\ down/ until...

\Thunder rumbles/ above. The smell of rain.

Sound off. Tick of Time echoes hall.

,,Fes, the Mike is the cone,'' Mary, behind the Pouncing Patti, taps (%). Pigtail still over shoulders. Hip swung to side. The fume of sweat flows forth. The receiver glides to Fes. The transmitter slides to Patti. 

Transmitter slides into Patti's redolence. Receiver glides upon granite...~spins~...

A Voice: ,,Fes, I know you're probably busy indexing for tonight but I think we should talk before you allow certain events to occur, because I also think you should know that I have changed my mind concerning that conversation of existence and where is I think I will be in ten years and
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
