<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="41" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
consuls corporations use of natural resources and currently consuls <i>Craft Store, Inc...</i>Fun,'' says Fes.

,,What is the note?'' Patti peers at the note. Fes reaches for the note. Patti allows the note to flow. The note floats.

,,Note...<i>C#</i>...the note that will fall flat because the note is too sharp.''

Patti fumes mint, lifts top (:smiles:) ,,What are you when you are fun?''

Fes taps wall ,,Mary, would you please entertain the guest,'' enters hall, opens closet door, removes the case, slams the door - shut...tips fescue, leaves Mary's shoes and masks indexed in hall...Two pictures fall: <i>Mary's Over The Grand Canyon</i> and <i>Mary Hidden In Field of Daisies</i>. Fes's case upon table. Fes sweeps away communion crumbs and droplets of tomato soup - <i>press the latches</i> - the case - opens, traces label, <i>Prerecord Events On Vinyl Studio In By Studio (An)other By (An)other</i> ''Who is the other...'' Mind 
held by the smell of rain. Soul by the sound of thunder.

Patti leans over, places elbows on table. Scent of flowers and dew fume. Shirt hangs. Image of Conceit cast against wall by electric shock. Finger runs upon Fes. Tongue moistens lips. Lips touch-

-Mary, can you answer the door? It is making a noise.'' 

Mary enters. Digits - <i>snap</i> - barrette (pigtail unwoven (waves evident)). Palm flat. Mary sneers ,,<i>Sure</i>, FES.''

Patti points to envelope purse, raises two digits, smiles, winks to Fes, pivots...taps ((echo)).

Fes runs digit upon envelope purse. Digit picks up strap and sets envelope purse on counter. Two digits unfasten zipper. Digit pulls flap back: A cloud of flowers and dew. The collection of the eye-liner, the mirror, the purple stick, the blush, the digital transmitter | receiver, the beaker. Fes pops the top of the beaker, taps the purple pills unto palm.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
