<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="43" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Fes throws stave wide ''What...HOW?'' Palm to mouth. Sight  upon  Leah.  Leah  takes  mark  and  scribes  ,,Shall  I play <i>Stormy Weather</i>, <i>Happy Birthday</i>? Maybe <i>Impossible </i> <i>Dream</i> or <i>So Long</i>...from the <i>Halls of Montezuma</i>...<i>Here </i> <i>Comes  the  Bride</i>?  <i>Her  name  is  Maria</i>?''  says  Leah ''However, I am missing <i>P5</i> and <i>M</i> (Sound off). Fes, you could not find it in <i>Bali Hai</i> or <i>Over the Rainbow</i> because we <i>see</i> colors''...and takes the red record...the fumes...the ~spins~ of the record red. ''You never play Alto.''

Fes flows to electric outlet. Throat clears and spit falls upon electric outlet. Fes writes above electric outlet: <i>Issues with  Power</i>.  Slaps  the  green  record  from  crate  ,,Thank YOU,'' teethes Fes, clears throat, spits upon electric cord. ''Is that what you want? An acoustic <i>perFOR</i>MANCE?''

Leah turns down volume with ,,<i>FE</i>S, I just want to <i>see</i> your sight's site cite during acoustic performances.''

Fes rushes through air of hall. Exhales, glides down hall skewing an image of Mary, <i>Blowing A Big Bubble of Gum</i>. Picture flows with fes to sun deck. Fes visors sight from the tip of sun's set. Squints for stars, whispers ,,<i>Never again</i>?''

<i>Never again?</i>

Hidden from their presence? 

<i>You lie.</i>

Because of the outer most sphere. 

Call it: ''<i>Antiphony</i>''

And at night?

Outside the house: Fes turns off water, places append-age on tip, drinks, swallows,  inhales, smiles, <i>sees</i> down hall...exhale echoes with ''Leah, how old is Simon? Is not Simon fifty-one?''

The distant reply of ,,<i>No, forty-three.</i>''

Steve walks by, smoke in mouth, digits about to strike match, turns, sight to ,,Fes, what time is it?''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
