<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="44" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
<i>Exhales... </i>,,<i>No</i>w.''

Pauses in Inhale w i t h ,,Y<i>es</i>,  n o w.''

,,Y<i>ou</i> a r e <i>correc</i>t,'' Fes exhales, clears, waves ((NO)), continues cant with ''I am trying to understand, <i>Steve</i>. But thoughts are becoming too unconventional,'' lost under the resonance of Leah and ,,<i>Mar</i>y, they'll never understand, in this day and age of hierarchies, that I belong on top and they on bottom.'' <i>Fes</i> to Steve as the wind pushes at the screen (Fes lowers the latch) and points down hall ,,<i>Too obvious</i>''...<i>sees</i> over indices...''Leah for example. Leah knows not (Steve exhales (too) ,,)<i>What time is i</i>t.'' Mary's voice conquers the wind ,,It is.'' Fes says ,,Thanks, Mary?'' whose talk below the breeze gains momentum then peaks ,,It must be Sara and Simon'' as Leah sings ,,Th<i>ey </i>b e l o n g <i>on </i>((bottom)).'' Steve claps(..) ,,Yes..They..Too..''

Fes sets glass down, leans against counter, stretches (Wind slams Screen) ,,Leah is intelligent. Lisa has issues.''

,,Yes..They..Too..''

Fes clears ,,Acts of righteous behavior convince <i>Leah</i> of Lisa's beliefs. Leah is thrilled. Tempo quickens. Peaks. Then they tap.''

,,Is Leah on top or bottom?'' laughs Steve, smothers smoke under sneaker, snubs the end, tosses the butt, lifts the latch\, pulls screen door and steps inside, waves away exhale, wipes feet, points to base of wall ''Oh, you...''

Fes waves `...you...' away ,,Only if you feel comfortable. You need not to take off the shoes,'' walks the kitchen, pours the water, voice echoes down the hall ,,((Fes))?''

,,Yes.''

,,Is Leah?''

Fes winks and smiles, spins two and half circles, taps hall wall tipping picture of Mary Hidden <i>From</i> Lense <i>Behind</i> Oak Tree ,,Is Leah what?''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
