<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="46" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
The reality. A desire. A need for the constant reassurance existence is within the cognate state. Too many fluxes of conscious and <i>subconscious</i>.

Leah and Mary walk in Palm in Palm. Leah says ,,Fes, what are you composing now?'' 

Fes blinks, <i>sees</i> to Patti. Patti (against the Ice Box) states ,,Cast into confrontation.''

,,Well, what are they confronting?'' says Leah.

Fes clenches jaw ,,Whatever it is they wish to hit they skip the truth to increase the span of the confrontation for the span of the issue is too skinny.'' Patti's redolence fumes ,,Sounds interesting.'' Fes's sight red. Fes's mind moves palms from jaw. The mouth wisps ,,In<i>terest</i> is the desire.''

Mary cradles Silence with palm while the other palm tosses Steve's crate key up\  and  down/ ,,May I?''

Fes points (<i>to</i>) ,,Take (<i>Silence and Leah</i>) with you.''

,,Group worship. No, I want Silence. Couples only.''

Fes froths Mary's fluff ,,Yes, you may. But please search for the key...if I remember the Mike recorded the Steve saying the key was lost.''

The Hug of Departure. Arms wide -|-, palms tap spine. The Social Concern for Well Being ''Shroud not you too deep tonight.'' The departure. Mary tells Leah and Patti ,,I may pause past and <i>see</i> you during the dawn. Call if interested. We will call Tomorrow,'' and cycles the index of items in briefcase, points ''<i>Fes</i>?'' who raises and hovers, floats to the Steve and the Clock, smiles ,,The pack. In the kitchen. Take the matches and the gum,'' <i>sees</i> out window to <i>see</i> Mary driving away, smiles ), peer(s) = the sand street with sight ''Have either of you had the pleasure of Mike?'' 

Fes leans upon wood rod, squints - - from the horizon fire, waves ''Mike (The smell of sage), Mary's an echo.''

Mike sweeps palm over scalp ,,That's not good.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
