<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="47" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
The Mike (T-shirt, blue jeans, leather sandals, shaved head, perpetually claps palms) slams the door - shut, takes the shoes - off, moves and lights a candle, places the palm above the flame of the candle, the laugh, the smile ''<i>Fes</i>, is the water in the Blue Box?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,Good.'' Patti winks ,,Fill it up after you pour it.'' Mike shakes head (up\ and down/), taps upon bathroom door, rubs scalp with palm, taps chin, leans upon closet door, holds out palm and walks over to ,,Patti, my name is Mike.''

Call it: ''Social <i>Pointer</i>''

And...then...the question: ,,Fes, where is Steve's 'O'ld machine!?'' 

Steve taps upon crate's frame: Turn| It| Down| So Fes Turns. It. Down, lis<i>ps</i> ,,<i>What</i> have you?'' ,,Where's my 'O'ld machine.'' ,,I know not. Mary guides old machine.'' ,,Why (arms X crossed, legs | | spread)? When I say Mary may guide my 'O'ld machine?'' Steve turns to ''Mike, you record me saying to Fes that only Fes was allowed to guide my 'O'ld machine?'' whips hip, bounces to stand and <i>sees</i> ''Fes. Where's my 'O'ld machine?''

Fes relaxes, pushes cone away ,,Come, Steve.'' They <i>see</i> through the window ''What you <i>see</i>?'' ,,A broken 'O'ld machine.'' ,,That is good you <i>see</i> a broken 'O'ld machine that will not marry Mary to merry and create a smile.'' 

Mary waves as Steve's Old Machine blurs by (cabin light on).

,,And what you <i>see</i> there?''

,,Mary waving, smiling, guiding Steve's 'O' l d Machine.'' Index: Finger: Hitting: <i>Fes</i>'s... 

Fes smiles at the stars ,,Well, it is good you said smiling.'' ,,'O'h...What time will Mary return 'O' l d Machine?''

Fes relaxes point ,,'O'h, well (:smiles:) when Mary is not married to merry by Steve's 'O'ld Machine.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>

