<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="48" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
,,'O'kay, Mary may also guide Steve's 'O'ld Machine.'' ,,I thank you,'' tone on High, points ''Yes, You May Sit There, but watch the indexes, please,'' spins ~Are~You~Welcome~, waits sixty|.........|.........|.........|.........|.........|.........|one tap(s) to say ''What time is it?''

,,Nine:forty-seven.'' ,,<i>No, it's ten:forty-</i>eight, Steve.'' ,,Will you will mercy for Steve, Fes?''

,,Yes, I will mercy for Steve. And thank you, Lisa,'' shakes loose ''Now, may I ask the other a question?''

,,Yes.'' 

,,What time you will we leave?''

,,<i>Twelve Taps</i>.'' ,,Twelve taps good, Steve?'' ,,Yes, INDEED.'' ,,Okay one hundred forty taps.'' (<i>Fes</i>) flows to the trash. Mike stands in Fes's flow and waves, blocks Fes's flow. Fes waves to the screen door ''The rubbish is beneath the stairs. Put the rubbish behind the palms. Thank you.''

Fes presses [On] [Off]. Increases amplification of p i T C h...Trails into plateau with random jungle |bass|. Spins (/below threshold of conscious sound): <i>Open that door</i> (rise of amplitude) Open that door ( /dips\ ) <i>Open that door</i> ( \lifts/ ) |BITCH|. I said <i>Open that door Open that door</i> Open that door, bitch. <i>Open that door Open that door</i>. Open that door ((<i>B I T C H</i>))|.....thank you good|.....Sir? ,,WHAT?'' ,,I thank you. Please close the screen door when you take the rubbish outside...(Call it: <i>Taking The White Trash Outside</i>)...And dig too long and I will you cut the grass.'' Fes taps counter, wisps ''<i>Turn it down</i>...thanks...(or Call it: Hyper-Content)...And close the screen door.''

Steve opens the window ,,May Mike inhale and exhale smoke in the (back) yard space?''

,,Yes, on the stone...too much pacing...put the rubbish in the shed in the box for rubbish please. And, please, tell Mike no casting stones across gravel way.''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
