<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="49" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Receiver blings. Fes sings ''<i>Will</i> I <i>see</i>  y o u there <i>to</i>niGHT?...((Good)),'' sets transmitter upon counter, walks to Room with Couch and Television, cuts: <i>Don't feel</i> Don't you ((feel)) <i>Don't feel</i> Don't you feel like <i>Don't you feel</i> (Turns up Sin) and FEEL ''Don't you feel like you want to fuck, AMEN||!||'' (Fes) ''<i>Yes</i>, <i>when I say yes</i>. Mike, Mary may be near tonight. Going to friend's house for fun.'' ,,You tell Mary I said Hi?'' The smell of cut grass overwhelms ,,What you say?'' ,,You tell Mary I said Hi?'' ,,No. I hear you not, so I speak you not.'' Fes turns off Air, walks to basin and lifts the water lever\. The water sprays. Fes takes flask marked `We' while the others marked `You' and rinses flask with water. Fes opens Blue Box, steadies flask, fills water to tip of flask, puts flask inside Blue Box - a draft - closes Blue Box and window, sweeps sand off deck, arranges circle of Confession Chairs to face Sand and White Picket Painted Gray - water marked horizon - stomps to stove, pivots, whips wave from toe to shoulder. Wave whips palm. Palm sets pan of water on stove, snaps, twists knob, ignites gas - <i>snap</i> - flame licks pan...water boils...drops cherries and leaves in water, claps while water simmers, lowers switches of deck (Vibrations, Reverb, Hi Hat, <i>Low</i> Tom) to a <i>whisper</i>: <i>You Don't you feel</i> you <i>Don't feel you feel Don't you feel Don't you feel </i>Don't you feel <i>Don't you feel like Don't you feel like</i> Don't you feel like <i>Don't you feel like a\</i> Fes smiles for break beat - a call for water - points to the tap ''And close the tap''...mind (re)minds to question...''What time is it?!'' ,,Nine:forty-eight!'' ,,Good, you now smell like a human.'' Fes taps [Stop], flows to kitchen window, points to can, lips ''<I will call you when I will we go>,'' taps on window, waves for ''Steve, no casting stones. Let the others exist and Mike will not throw stones back.'' A wave of <Thank>. Transmitter placed atop Blue |-|Box|-| for Ice.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
