<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="50" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Mind cites<i> Song for The Last Supper</i>.

Receiver ~vibrates~. Fes reverbs ''Yes (changes upright flow to a slouched wave, ||claps|| hat^, laughs) Yes, Mike said `hi'...yes...yes...maybe...You will it...yes...I know, Mike is <i>fucked</i>.'' Receiver tossed to floor.

Then there was Sound. An electronic discharge of fact. Felt and heard, screams: YOU NEED NOT TO POUND THE KEYS TO SAY 'NO!' 

Stop. Record. Slow the tempo. Loop.

Fes <i>sees</i> outside and witnesses Stones Flying, By Unaware Guests Smoking <Across Gravel Way>. The dis-charge: STOP! Fes casts the phase and catches the reverb (the reaction of the phase) for an electric charge to secure the act of the moment. Fes needed to laugh - laughed. Fes felt the emotion and the need to cry - laughed. Fes ponders the emotional reaction and wishes mind had allowed sorrow to exist. Shoulders shrug in sorrows stead. Fes spins upon the Black and White Tile - frozen at half-mast - turns down sound - all sight unseen - strolls to the Cracked Mirror, commands: ''Mike, tell the others across gravel way the tale of Steve, a psychologic-hypochondriac.'' 

Steve tells Mike Steve's sensitive and ,,...if I'm emotionally scrapped I could be infirm for days and maybe die.'' Mike leans against tree and shakes head ,,Is that the standard these days?''

Lights scan Couch and Television Room. Hall glows, dims. Doors shut. Steps tap. A knock of door.

Fes taps ,,Tomatoes. Mangos. Peaches. I shall peel an orange and squirt the cherries. The tomatoes on the side''...waves out window...''Wine and fruit await. If you step inside I shall serve you.''

Mike distinguishes the smoke: Exhales... ,,The apple?'' ...lifts latch\. Mike pulls (back) screen door.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
