<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="51" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Steve, Patti and Leah take hardwood bowls with fruit, sit upon Couch and Television Room's Floor and chomp to flip of pop-scripts (talk of fashion fumes forth).

...Fes smiles for ,,Mike, Mary holds the apple.''

(Another) knock of door. Fes smiles ''Patti, while Mary is displaced could you please answer the taps upon door?''

,,Yea.''

Fes's sight crosses, brow wrinkles.

Patti grins ''Yes...Fes,'' and opens the door.

Pop-script-pages flip. Steve's sight to ,,Fes, where is the soap and water''...and to the door to bellow...''S -N- S.''

Sara -n- Simon (sight aware of life, step light, have dimples, hand -n- hand, wear matching yellow glasses, baggy trousers, pullovers, always witness the other in the sight while smiling, talk to the other in <i>nascent</i> <i>nascent </i>tones) sing in unison to ,,Fe<i>S</i>, h`O'w are ((you)) ~<i>NOW</i>~?'' Sara laughs, smiles toward ,,Fes, you remember (Simon)?''

,,Yes! (posture erects) Simon,'' wisps Fes <i>I was pleased to meet you.</i>''

Steve motions: <Good?>.

Fes shakes: <No>, says ''How was the flight?''

Simon spins digit: <~Good~>.

Fes smiles <YES>, says ''Maybe,'' (to Sara) whispers to Steve's ear ''<i>Recite the pop-script</i>.'' An electric discharge. Steve reads: ,,Simon says, Simon thinks, Simon moves and Simon says `Where am I'?''

''Where am I?'' says Steve.

Mike replies ,,The Fes House.''

Sara's frame stiffens. Blood vessels pump. Ears perk. The face wares smirk. The smirk : |.

The charge Across Gravel Way ,,TOO LOUD!''

(Fes presses [Mute].) 

The discharge (Across Gravel Way): ,,THANK YOU!''
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
