<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="53" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
The door shall remain open so I can hear you scream.'' 

Fes rotates disk afore ''Sara, what you will we play.'' Sara indexes disk, points ,,Yes, here, here and here. But only four break beats and a low clap.'' Fes taps, shakes digit ,,Then the taps shall exist. Thank you.'' An electric discharge. Volume set to High ''And remember to breathe when Simon casts illusions of three dimensions''...flows through hall to pot of cherries upon flame...''Hot cherry tea? The hot cherry tea will relax the muscle. The hot cherry tea may prevent hyperventilation when we forget to inhale <i>-n-</i> exhale or cast illusions...The hot cherry tea is good.'' 

Space - quiet. Minds on the tasks of digits (Rotates): <i>feel like you want </i>feel like you want <i>to feel you have to pound the keys</i> you have to pound the keys <i>don't feel like you</i> don't feel like you have to pound the keys to say GO. Loops reverb. Stops motion. Waves for count. A run of indices ''Thanks.'' Feel the drop. The rise. The peak. The plateau. The descent with the other. Or upon the other...

Mike taps Fes... 

Fes stands ''What?!''

,,It is time.''

,,What time is it?''

Mike taps wrist and points to the analog synth-sonus-machine, the two rotating discs...the eco.

''Yes...I know.''

,,Good.''

Fes smiles ,,Yes. Steve -n- Mike pull plugs from sockets and roll electric cords into the box, please,'' places two indices atop electric cords, latches cover/, stretches, balances, waves through space ''Where is the fescue?''

Fes walks to Mary's pile of indexed attire arranged by sight outside hall closet, files through red, orange, yellow, green, blue, indigo and a pair of violet masks - sneezes.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
