<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="55" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
upon the flame. Fes lifts pot of cherries -n- leaves and pours hot cherry tea in flask marked `You'. 

The Outside: Sun disappears below <i>Horizon of Silicon</i>.

The Inside: Fes swallows the hot cherry tea. Nerves settle. Muscles relax. Veins pump. Waves flow under skin. Balance wavers. Heavy with <i>em</i>pathy. Sight wanders. Smell clouds. Taste blends. Touch numbs. The mind hones action. Tense becomes a fluid path of faith-action in the confines of a flow primed to calculate the dance for the other. <i>Fes</i> will <i>sing</i>. Fes will sing for the other for nothing will exist but the other. The other will exist through a filtered perception of senses honed for social direction. The senses honed to tap the tap of carnal stimulation and momentary satisfaction of time and location through the euphoria of the manufactured <i>bliss</i> pressed and packaged for human consumption.

<i>Fes </i>smiles for the tap of song and dance, sets glass upon counter top, clears counter. Sings. The Wind Stops.

The Sight that is Steve <i>flow</i>s in ,,Good Times?''

<i>Fes</i> grins ,,<i>Well</i>, I call the tap of time more warm or hot...maybe. Red if you <i>see.</i> Steve, have you <i>seen</i> the fescue?''

Steve pivots to akimbo stance, falls soft to a postured lean, sets hand upon hip ,,I think the fescue is in the other room. I witnessed Leah...Lisa...never...put the fescue in the other room a tap ago (Steve pushes glasses (back)). Leah's a played bitch.'' Fes taps Steve ,,You believe every bitch is played.'' 

Call it: ''<i>...On The Way Out</i>''

Over (back) ,,Well, you're right, but so am I. So cast a stone at an object worthy of tapping practice.'' <i>Fes</i> flows through the hall ,,<i>Steve</i>, I believe you <i>see</i> truth.'' 

...taps...

Steve's M||O||an ||Rattles||.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
