<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="56" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
Fes whispers reply of ''<i>Too much fun</i>...''

The Band: A circle in the middle of the space. A joint passed around the parameter of the band. A shroud of silk lay  in  the  center  of  the  band.  Fes  (whose  shoulders  fall) pushes an index (back), lays on the couch to watch the fan spin above the band ''What time is it?''

Mike coughs, places fist over mouth, holds lungs ,,It's almost time to go (throat gags, lips taut, exhales...) We're almost finished and then I will we go.''

Leah inhales and waves redolence toward ,,Fes, you want any?''

,,No. Thank you.'' 

Leah stands and sits by Fes's stomach and exhales upon ,,Fes, you no?''

Fes smiles ,,Yes, I know my will.'' 

Leah rubs over Fes and runs over Fes's tip...taps... ,,You feel good?''

Headlights spot window. Leah's shadow cast on wall.

,,Yes, just tying to remember where I put the fescue.''

,,Getting stoned and old are you?''

,,I am not petrified and I am not insulted by words. Are you calling me old?''

,,No longer naïve?''

,,Yes,'' Fes props, points to the band ''I am.''

Leah's shadow cuddles in corner of couch, pulls back stave, sight lost in the silhouette horizon ,,What's the Veil of Illusion for?''

Fes sits up, arches back along arm of couch, <i>sees</i> ,,...for <i>her</i>.''

Lisa flashes lashes ,,And if you <i>hear</i> her <i>not</i> her?''

,,I will the illusion to <i>you</i>.'' Fes smiles, <i>sees</i> her- <i>aw</i>AY!

Lisa waves off turn for inhale ,,We go.''

,,||GO||!'' echoes Steve's Shout.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
