<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE Lacivious SYSTEM "lacivious.dtd">
<Lacivious>
<page number="57" authors="Kalab J. Oster">
The Mike conducts. Mike points. They distinguish. The burn off of flesh. Pants brushed. Jackets arranged. A spray of mint. A dash of sage and fire smoke. All minds search for a focus. No contact in the silence of the moment, a need for social guidance, a desire to remain within the haven of familiar surroundings and wait, if only for a moment, to ponder the objective for the night, until the... 

,,Have you <i>seen</i> the fescue?'' 

Leah pulls the fescue from the sofa and gives the fescue to the Steve ,,'O'H I gave the fescue to your BITCH, <i>Fes</i>. No<i>W every</i>One will have sympathy for the Steve 'O'.'' 

Fes - <i>snap</i> - <shakes> (side to side), taps to door then opens door ,,Is everything upon the deck?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,Simon.'' ,,Yes.'' ,,Are you guiding us this evening?'' ,,Yes, The <i>Rain</i>bow Con <i>nec</i> tion.'' ,,Was that once The Es ta blish ment?'' ,,Yes, but The Establishment closed for business.'' ,,Years a g o.'' ,,<i>I never</i> we<i>NT</i>.'' ,,Years a go.'' ,,I had heard they wanted the establishment to become that.'' ,,That never ||<i>WENT</i>||.'' ,,Why not?'' ,,The Mike.'' ,,The Establishment peaked too soon.'' ,,Who is guiding?'' ,,<i>Steve</i> -n- I.'' ,,Steve, you have digits?'' ,,Yes.'' ,,Are you good to guide?'' (digits on tip) ,,Of course, please Fes I was <i>good whE</i>N I arrived.'' ,,What time is it?'' ,,NIne:FiFty-s<i>ix</i>.'' ,,Ten : <i>fi f</i>ty-s e v e n.'' ,,Steve, are you sure you are good?'' ,,Yes, I am good... <i>Si</i>m'O'n...and <i>you</i> good and want to go?'' ,,Sara?'' 

Rhythmic index of sound vibrates \roof/ and |-|walls|-|. Pictures of the Ivy Gates -n- Halos skew. Heads bop and staves slide for door. Stacks of crates in machine. The Night of Sabbath wait the minds that follow the other. Fes opens a window, rolls silk, puts silk in pack, takes out flyer... 

Softfloor is in the hidden amplitudes 

<i>Go</i> 
 
And find the Illusion.
</page>
<copyright title="Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License" story="Lacivious" writers="Kalab J. Oster" holders="Kalab J. Oster">
copyright (C) 2016 Kalab J. Oster

Permission is granted by the Copyright Holders for humans or other intelligent agents to read, write, edit, publish and critique the Story if the humans or intelligent agents keep this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License with the Story if not the page, and if another writer writes or edits the Story then the writer's name needs to be appended to the end of the Writer list of this Word Prostitute(R) Open Story License.
</copyright>
</Lacivious>
